aseohosting.com 2012-12-12

# Seo hosting privacy policy statement | Aseohosting client protection

Your privacy policy must state that no information submitted by a buyer will not be shared, sold, reused in lists, or be used for any other purpose than to complete a transaction or address a customer service concern. The following is an example privacy policy, you may replace aseohosting.com with your website name if you would like to use it as the privacy policy on your site.

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

aseohosting.com values the privacy and security of the information that you share with us through aseohosting.com. It is important that you understand how we collect, use, and maintain your information. This Privacy Statement explains our online information practices, the choices you may make about how we collect and use your information at this Web Site, and the ways you may contact us.

We may change this Privacy Statement from time to time. Changes to this Privacy Statement are effective upon posting. Please check back periodically for updates.

**Definitions :**  
”Personal Information” includes, your name, address information, personal e-mail address and URL, telephone number, account username and password, as well as other, similar information.  
”Prospect Information” includes the same information as Personal Information except that Prospect Information is information that is submitted by an individual who is not the subject of the data submitted.  
”Non-Identifying Personal Information” includes information about you, including, without limitation, your Internet service provider, browser type, domain name, the Web Site that referred you to us, the web pages you request, the date and time of those requests, and entry and exit points.  
Collection of Personal Information or Prospect Information  
aseohosting.com may collect Personal Information from you, but only if you provide it to us voluntarily. We also collect Personal Information that you provide to us so that we can fulfill your order. In addition, in certain situations, such as when a purchaser buys a product as a gift and supplies the recipients’ name and address, we collect Prospect Information.  
Collection and Use of Non-Identifying Personal Information  
During your use of our Web Site, we will collect certain Non-Identifying Personal Information to enhance the functionality of the Web Site and to make your access more convenient and efficient. We retain Non-Identifying Personal Information and use it to establish Web Site activity trends, monitor Web Site performance, improve Web Site design and functionality, fulfill orders, inform current and potential customers and suppliers about our services, and for other business purposes. Our collection of Non-Identifying Personal Information may involve the use of cookies. Among other uses, cookies allow us to deliver content specific to your interests, to save you from re-entering your registration data at each connection, and to provide features such as online customer payment and shopping carts. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to configure your web browser to accept cookies, to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or to disable cookies altogether. No personal or unencrypted information will be encoded in cookies that are stored on your computer.

**Children**  
aseohosting.com does not sell products for purchase by children, but we do sell children's products for purchase by adults. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information or Prospect Information from children under age 13. If you are under age 13, do not share personal information with us.

**Use of Personal Information :**  
aseohosting.com may use and disclose Personal Information or Prospect Information as described in this document. In addition to the uses described in this document, we may use Personal Information or Prospect Information for purposes that include maintaining the Web Site, order fulfillment and administration, and product surveys, administrative and analytical purposes like accounting, billing and audits, and information system management, and other, similar uses. We may also use Personal Information or Prospect Information to provide current and potential customers and suppliers with information about our services.  
We only collect, use, and disclose Personal Information or Prospect Information for purposes that are reasonable in the circumstances. We use only fair and lawful means to collect Personal Information or Prospect Information.

**Protection of aseohosting.com and Others :**  
We may use or disclose Personal Information or Prospect Information without your consent in certain circumstances:  
\- If we are required by law or by an order or requirement of a court, administrative agency, or other government entity, or by court rules concerning the production of records;  
\- If we have reasonable grounds to believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, privacy, property, or safety of our users or others;  
\- If we have reasonable grounds to believe that the information relates to breach of an agreement or violation of the law that has been, is being, or is about to be committed;  
\- If it is necessary for fraud protection, risk reduction, or the establishment or collection of funds owed to us;  
\- If it is necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, to pursue remedies, or to limit damages to 2Checkout;  
\- If the information is public;  
\- For other reasons allowed or required by law.

When we are required or permitted to disclose information without consent, we will not disclose more information than is necessary to fulfill the disclosure purpose.
